https://www.dmmcu.org/resources-2/privacy-notice/

MENUMENUhomeEn Español
Abrir Una CuentaPréstamosPréstamo LograCréditoAplicar para un préstamoEnterprise Car Sales_EspañolCuentas de AhorrosCuentas de ChequesTarjeta CooperaAquí Para La ComunidadTestimonios De Miembros
Loans
Apply for a LoanApply For A Mortgage LoanLoan RatesAuto LoansShop For A CarEnterprise Car SalesFirst Mortgage LoansHome Equity LoansPersonal LoansBuilding CreditMastercardSmall Business LoansStudent Loans
Accounts
SavingsCertificatesIRAKirby Kangaroo ClubPersonal CheckingBusiness CheckingDeposit RatesFee Schedule
Services
E-ServicesShared BranchingVisa Prepaid Reloadable CardVisa Gift CardsProtect Your LoansInsurance ServicesOther Services
Resources
Find an ATMFind a Shared BranchCredit SenseAutoSMARTReorder ChecksWire InstructionsFinancial CalculatorsAnnual Credit ReportNewsletterPrivacy Notice
About Us
Contact UsBecome a MemberCredit Union HistoryMember TestimonialsCareersAccessibilitySite Map
Online Banking
Account Login
Credit Card Login
Apply for Loan
Search
Privacy Notice
Des Moines Metro Credit Union Privacy Policy
FACTS
WHAT DOES DES MOINES METRO CREDIT UNION (DMMCU) DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
WHY?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
WHAT?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number
Loss History
Payment History
Credit History
Transaction History
Overdraft History
HOW?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons DMMCU chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does DMMCU share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you
Yes
Yes
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
Yes
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
Information about your transactions and experiences
No
We don’t share
QUESTIONS?
Call 515-283-4195 or 1-877-715-9604
WHO WE ARE
Who is providing this notice?
Des Moines Metro Credit Union
WHAT WE DO
How does DMMCU protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
DMMCU also maintains other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom access is appropriate.
How does DMMCU collect my personal information?
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
Affiliates from using your information to market to you
Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
DMMCU has no affiliates.
Non-affiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
DMMCU has no non-affiliates
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
CUNA Mutual Group
Affinion
